Does that mean Major General Karen
這麼說來 卡連連隊長
was against the New Himuka Government's method?
反對新日向政府的作法嗎
No...
不…
It's finally here.
終於出現了
There seems to be more that we don't know
似乎有什麼內幕
about Karen's true intention
卡連真正的用意
and his...
定還有他…
Chief Sumeragi!
皇本部長
A large number of Others are invading Central Suoh!
大量的怪異 侵入蘇芳的中央部
What?
什麼
Eliminate the enemies at once.
盡快殲滅怪異
But our defense system is not working.
可是 防衛系統毫無動作
Psynet is offline too.
超腦網路也斷線了
What about the council?
評議會呢
We don't know.
不清楚
We couldn't contact them.
完全聯絡不上
Could this be... Arahabaki...
不會吧…荒吐神竟然…
Karen, how did it turn into this mess?
卡連 為何會變成這樣
I will get it back this time.
這次 我必定能奪回
Yuito!
…結人
What's wrong with you? Don't let your guard down!
你怎麼了 別大意
Okay.
好
Wataru, do you hear me?
渡 快回答
What is going on?
這是…怎麼回事
Wataru?
渡
No, we can't reach him.
不行 沒有回應
Psynet is offline.
超腦網路斷線了
Yuito, stay alert.
結人 你們小心
Wataru?
渡
Arahabaki that was controlling Suoh is down.
控制著蘇芳京的荒吐神斷線
This is an emergency.
情況很危急
We don't know what caused it yet.
目前還不知原因為何
But the defense system has stopped working.
但防衛系統也因此停止運作
The Others are using this opening to invade.
造成怪異入侵市區
Wait, Wataru. What is going on now?
等等 渡 現在是怎麼回事
I'm contacting you via telepathy.
這是我傳給你的心電感應
I'll see if I can get psynet back online.
我去調查超腦網路是否能恢復
Haruka already went out...
遙已經到外面去了…
What?
什麼
Seiran garrison has got the headquarters surrounded.
青藍軍 包圍了本部
What are you doing here?
你在那裡幹嘛
Wataru?
渡
Yuito, eliminate the Others as soon as you can.
結人你們先盡量解決怪異
Do your best to survive.
大家努力活下去
This could likely be a coup d'état!
我想這應該是…政變
Wataru?
渡…
What's wrong?
什麼 怎麼了
He contacted me via telepathy.
渡用心電感應傳訊息給我
Arahabki is offline.
說荒吐神斷線
That caused psynet and the defense system to go offline.
造成超腦網路和防衛系統無法運作
There seems to be a coup d'état.
似乎是起了政變
A coup d'état?
政變
Does that mean Major General Karen...
意思是 卡連連隊長他…
They even went this far...
竟然做到這種地步
Yuito, if Major General Karen is plotting a coup d'état...
結人 卡連連隊長 打算起政變的話…
Father...
爸爸…
SCARLET NEXUS
《緋紅結繫》
♫A crime in reality♫
現實的Crimｅ
♫For Heaven's sake♫
For Heaven's sake
♫Accepts any fake♫
接受虛假
♫And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♫
永恆的幻想 層層逝去
♫Won't take it at all, I get sick♫
絕非完美 I get sick
♫A girl looking back♫
轉身而來的少女
♫Casts the miracle into the instant world♫
在這瞬息世界中 落下了奇蹟
♫Did you lie♫
Did you lie
♫Spit the venom♫
Spit the venom
♫I know why♫
I know why
♫I've found a game of ecstasy♫
找到了 絕頂的遊戲
♫Red Criminal gets life♫
Red Criminal gets life
♫I've never been in love♫
I've never been in love
♫Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♫
我何時開始厭倦了這樣的世界
♫We will fly♫
We will fly
♫Someday I won't be crying♫
Someday I won't be crying
♫I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♫
為了不再傷害 而犧牲了自己
KAREN'S BETRAYAL
(卡連的叛亂)
There are more of them.
還有嗎
Leave them to me.
我來
Yuito...
結人…
About your father...
你不去找叔叔…
Aren't you going to meet up with Chairman Sumeragi?
去找皇評議會議長嗎
Yuito must be worried about them.
結人…一定也很擔心皇本部長
He wants to carry out his duty.
他定是想做好份內任務
What happened?
發生什麼事了
You lost contact with them?
無法取得聯繫
What was the cause?
這是怎麼回事
It's the jamming signal.
電波受到干擾的緣故
We lost contact with the whole army.
目前 全軍都無法取得聯繫
Who could have pulled this off?
到底是誰搞的鬼
Connected. Casting the image now.
接上了 轉接影像
Via traffic cameras,
透過交通監視器
we found the image before the jamming signal cut us off.
我們找到干擾前的影像
"SEIRAN FORCE" It's the Seiran Garrison.
(青藍軍) 敵方是青藍軍
Sorry for interrupting, Chief Sumeragi.
打擾了 皇本部長
The backup of psynet and other online data is complete.
超腦網路的備份 以及其他無線資訊 全數完成
As you know, the Seiran garrison has us surrounded.
如您所知 我們被青藍軍包圍
The underground evacuation route...
而地下的緊急避難路線…
How likely are the enemies going to spot us?
被敵人得知的機率很高
After all, the OSF is now divided into two factions.
畢竟怪伐軍都被分為兩派了
What about the council?
評議會呢
We haven't managed to get a hold
包含皇評議會議長的消息
of Chairman Sumeragi's situation.
目前仍無法掌握
Why are you launching a coup, Major General Karen?
卡連連隊長…為什麼要搞政變
The man who terminated the Other in one strike
一擊消滅怪異的是
No.1 of the Septentrion,
榮獲七劍星一等勳章的
Brain Eater Major General Karen Travers!
噬腦者 卡蓮崔佛斯少將
He is so cool.
好帥喔
The nation is under the constant invasion of the Others.
然而在這頻繁受到 怪異威脅的國家中
The scouted soldiers who possess outstanding power
天生擁有優秀超腦力之人的招募組
and volunteer soldiers who train extensively to hone their power,
及藉由鍛鍊提升腦力的志願組
must work as one.
不分彼此
Unless we combine all of our strength...
如不結合各自的腦力…
Private Yuito Sumeragi.
結人 皇上等兵
Yes?
是
Major General Karen!
卡連連隊長
You're already making headlines right after your enlistment.
才剛入伍 就被媒體追捧
Yes.
是
Make use of the media's attention.
試著反過來利用媒體資源
The more fame you gather, the faster you get promoted.
越多人知道你的名字 階級昇得越快
Joining Seto Platoon will help you learn better.
加入賽特小隊 能幫助你增加不少實力
Give it your best.
多多努力吧
I have high hopes for you.
我期待你的表現
Thank you!
謝謝
Great job, Yuito.
結人 太好了
Major General Karen has had his eyes on you since you were still a cadet.
卡連連隊長 從你還是訓練生時 就很看好你了
Really?
真的嗎
The No.1 of the Septentrion expects great things from you.
是啊 你受到七劍星一等勳章的 連隊長所期待
Give it your all.
要好好加油喔
Yes!
是
Why was Nagi acting so strange?
那歧變得如此奇怪
Did the government do something to him?
也是被新日向政府 動了什麼手腳嗎
What could have made Major General Karen go as far as to launching a coup?
是什麼 讓卡連連隊長 做到這個地步
Father must know something.
爸爸 一定知道什麼
There is no end to this.
真是的 沒完沒了
What's wrong?
怎麼了
Major General Fubuki is coming.
吹雪連隊長來了
He's right ahead of us.
就在正前方
Which platoon do you belong now?
你們 現在隸屬哪個小隊
Well... We...
那個…我們現在…
Captain Seto was killed in action.
賽特隊長 戰死了
Seto was killed in action?
賽特戰死了
Wait. Is your commanding officer Karen?
等等 你們的指揮官是卡連嗎
No.
不…不是
Major General Fubuki, allow me to explain.
吹雪連隊長 我來說明吧
I see.
原來如此
No other member was summoned except for Gemma, right?
除了蓋曼之外 其他隊員都沒被召集嗎
Yes.
是的
And now you've joined hands with Yuito and the others.
而你現在與結人他們一起行動
So you're not on Karen's side.
表示你不站在卡連那邊
Does that sum up the situation?
我這樣理解沒錯吧
Yes.
沒錯
I see. We need more soldiers.
我知道了 現在需要更多同伴
From now on, you belong to my platoon.
從現在起 你們隸屬我的部隊
Yes.
是
I haven't got a hold of the whole situation.
我尚未掌握所有情況
All we are certain for now is that members of OSF have defected to Seiran.
目前只確定 青藍軍與部分人士勾結
They were instigated by Karen
受到卡連的煽動
and laid waste to the whole Suoh.
襲擊了整個蘇芳
Innocent lives were caught up in this mess.
連市民都被無辜捲入
Everyone is leading the civilians to safety.
現在 大家正分頭帶領市民去避難
But I have another mission for you.
不過 我想讓你們執行別的任務
Make sure Chairman Sumeragi and the council members are safe.
確認皇評議會議長一行人的安危
The Chairman and members of the council weren't evacuated immediately.
評議會議長及數名議員 遲遲尚未避難
They are still on their way to a shelter.
目前似乎還在往避難所的路上
OSF and the National Defense Forces are en route.
怪伐軍及國防軍都趕了過去
But we lost contact.
但卻失去了聯繫
It will be a relief for the Chairman if you're there.
你們過去幫忙 議長應該也比較安心
Understood.
我知道了
Stay cautious.
自己多加小心
Not all members of OSF are on our side.
並非所有怪伐軍都是同伴
The Seiran garrison isn't making a move.
青藍軍 仍然沒有任何動作
Are they buying time?
他們是否在爭取時間
We don't know.
不知道
Karen has trapped us in here.
卡連封住我們行動
But what is his motive?
到底目的是什麼
Brother...
哥哥…
Things have got out of hand.
事情演變得好嚴重喔
This place is like a ghost town.
街道都變成這副模樣
Is this the world people without power see?
這就是沒有腦力的人 看到的世界嗎
The Bell Peppers can't connect to psynet.
畢竟甜椒們 無法連上超腦網路
-Luka! -Have you located Karen?
-魯卡 -知道卡連的去向了嗎
We haven't found anything yet.
尚未找到任何線索
Where is my brother?
哥哥在何處
What is he planning now?
之後又打算做什麼
I couldn't contact Kagero and Kyoka either.
甚至連陽炎和鏡花他們的消息 我都無法掌握
Kasane!
重
What is it? Is everything online again?
怎麼了 復原了嗎
No, this is...
不 這是…
-Major General Karen! -Brother...
-卡連連隊長 -哥哥
Blinded citizens of New Himuka
盲目的新日向國民們
and the foolish people who choose to ignore the harsh side of reality.
以及 選擇視而不見的愚蠢人們
I am Karen Travers.
我是卡連崔佛斯
Objecting the New Himuka administration and its conducts
因否定新日向政治管理方針
has opened my eyes.
而覺醒之人
Well? Is everything back to normal?
怎麼 好了嗎
It's Master Karen.
是卡連大人
Blinded citizens of New Himuka
盲目的新日向國民們
and the foolish people who choose to ignore the harsh side of reality.
以及 選擇視而不見的愚蠢人們
I am Karen Travers.
我是卡連崔佛斯
Objecting the New Himuka administration and its conducts
因否定新日向政治管理方針
has opened my eyes.
而覺醒之人
My comrades and I
我跟我的同志們
have formed an alliance with the Seiran garrison who share our vision and goal.
決心與志向一致的青藍市結盟
Pitiful citizens of New Himuka.
可悲的新日向國民們
Accept the reality before you.
別否認眼前的事實
This country has gone insane.
這個國家早已瘋狂
The New Himuka Government
新日向政府
move society forward with the integration of psynet.
藉由超腦網路發展社會
As we all know,
如大家所知
the heart of psynet
超腦網路的中心
is Arahabaki, the city-size computer.
是都市電腦 荒吐神
Almost everyone in this country and people with power
幾乎所有國民 以及腦力擁有者
have their brains connected to Arahabaki.
大家的腦都與荒吐神相連
It gives you the convenience of browsing and using all sorts of functions and information.
因此 國民能任意瀏覽並利用 各種場所及資訊
You led a life of freedom.
過著自由自在的生活
But that is not true freedom!
然而 這並不是真正的自由
What does he mean?
怎麼回事
The government has access to all the information.
所有情報都經過政府管控
The citizens are being monitored like cattle.
而國民則被政府豢養著
It's time to face this fact.
請正視這個問題
All humans
所有的人類
are only alive for the benefit of this country and its government.
都是為了國家 為了政府 而生 而利用的家畜
They silence anyone that will challenge the system.
他們排除會動搖體制的人
They change the people's personalities,
改變其性格
making the people their loyal pawns.
讓其自願成為棋子
They turn the people into their faithful cattle.
並培養成順從體制的家畜
The New Himuka Government doesn't deserve our trust!
這樣的新日向政府毫無道義可言
Now is the time to stand up and fight.
現在正是站起來
It's time to overthrow this government.
打倒新日向政府的時候
This can't be happening.
怎麼會
They are here.
來了
Yuito, go to Chairman Sumeragi at once.
結人 你快去皇評議會議長的身邊
Leave the enemies to us.
這裡交給我們
Go!
快去吧
Open your eyes, people of the New Himuka Government.
快醒來吧 新日向的國民
The city of Seiran will defend the right to free will.
青藍市會守護人類的自由意志
We will provide the people with the rights they deserve.
並提供人類真正該有的生活環境
And you have my word.
而我 在此向大家保證
All those who are willing to follow my cause
願意與我們同行之人
will not require any qualification.
不需要任何的資格
Are you all right?
沒事吧
Yeah.
沒事…
The Others are headed
其他怪異群
to the shelter where the Chairman
正往評議會議長們前進的…
and the council members are going.
避難所的方向
Father...
爸爸
I've made up my mind.
我已經決定了
I don't care what you say about it.
不管爸爸說什麼
I want to join OSF.
我都要加入怪伐軍
Your power compatibility is too low. So you can stop daydreaming now.
你的超腦力適性過低 就別妄想了
The fact you haven't been scouted proves my point.
證據就是你到這個年紀 仍尚未被招募
Then I'll just have to join as a volunteer soldier and accept my training.
只要以志願軍的身分接受訓練 就能解決這個問題
I'll prove my worth to you!
我會證明給你看的
Have you ever consider
你有考慮過
what your mother would say if she was still alive?
如果你媽還活著 會怎麼說
Do you think she would be proud of you?
你認為你媽會為你高興嗎
Whatever the government did to us,
就算政府做了什麼
he is still my father.
爸爸仍是我爸爸
Congratulations on your enlistment.
恭喜你正式入伍
But I'm still against this decision.
雖然 我還是反對你進怪伐軍
Make sure not to get yourself hurt.
但至少別受傷了
You're now a member of OSF.
既然已是怪伐軍的成員
That means you can hold your own.
就表示你也獨當一面了
I want to use this chance to talk about our family and your late mother.
趁這個機會 我想跟你聊聊 家裡的事及你已逝世的母親
We should ask Kaito to join us for dinner next time.
下次找上界人 一起吃頓飯吧
I'll be in touch.
我再跟你聯絡
I stand at Seiran's frontline.
我站在青藍的前線
I'm against the notion of being controlled by a handful of powerful men.
揮舞著反抗少數人掌握權力 控制社會的革命旗幟
From now on, Seiran is my home.
從現在起 青藍便是我的故鄉
I will crumble New Himuka's system.
我將打倒新日向的體制
From now on,
現在開始
I will break free from the control of darkness.
我等將脫離躲在暗中的支配
This is a war of our revolution.
這是場革命戰爭
Those who have opened their eyes and those who wish to see the truth...
覺醒之人 欲覺醒之人
-Over here! -Come to me.
-請到這裡 -來到我身邊
Come to Seiran.
聚集到青藍
Together, we will strike down
讓我們一同討伐
New Himuka's corrupted system!
新日向的體制
Over here, hurry!
快到裡面去
Wait for me...
等我…
What?
什麼
You are...
你是…
Kasane?
重…
How did you get here?
妳怎麼會在這
Father...
爸爸…
♫I don't need to let fate dictate me♫
無須被命運所指使
♫Because I believe that I can rewrite it♫
相信定會被改寫
♫I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♫
讓我們今後 繼續做著夢
♫Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♫
朝陽正光輝燦爛 隨後落下
♫What's waiting for us at the world's end♫
在世界的盡頭 究竟等著什麼
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going♫
未來 燈火永恆不滅
♫Who can shake us♫
誰在威脅我們
♫Who can define us♫
誰為我們決定
♫It's nothing less than our story♫
這是屬於我們的故事
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♫
未來 你心中的燈火永恆不滅
A TOMORROW OF RUIN
(破滅的明日)